hoparoundindia.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy Hoparoundindia.com

The Policy deals with the analysis of personally identifiable information collected by **HopAroundIndia.com** , when you access our website. This policy does not apply to any entity not owned or controlled by the Company. This Policy may not be applicable to any information provided by you or on your behalf to **HopAroundIndia.com** in any other context. By accessing the website or any website of the Company, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy. 

Specific Information

We collect some personal information from our registered users to avail certain services provided by **HopAroundIndia.com**. The specific information that is provided by our registered users is- Name, Age/Date of Birth, E-mail, Gender, Marital Status, Anniversary, Occupation, address and Holiday Preferences. 

**HopAroundIndia.com** also uses the personal information collected from users to fulfill user requests for certain information, products and services; and to update them on the latest news and offerings from **HopAroundIndia.com**.

General Information   
This website may also capture certain generic identifiable information about user's access to the website including the IP address through which this site is accessed, the time at which this site is accessed and the specific parts of the website accessed by users. This information is used by us for enhancing of the website and for identifying the most frequently visited parts of the website, which is kept confidential and is not shared with any third parties.

Third party Information   
Promotional offers provided on **HopAroundIndia.com** are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties for which they may obtain information that user's voluntarily submit to participate in their programs/activities. We have no control whatsoever over the use of these information as we encourage you to refer to their respective privacy policies for more information on their privacy practices.

Cookies   
The website uses cookies to enhance the quality of access of our website and make it more convenient. The information previously provided by users may be retrieved by their respective computers/laptops to enable certain features of the site without having to re-sign in, and allow them to customize or access certain parts of the website such as automatic sign- in to **HopAroundIndia.com**. The cookies would be stored on the hard disk of their computer or laptop and the acceptance of cookies is dependent on the web-browser settings used by users.

Usage of Information  
Users personally identifiable information will not be sold or rented to anyone by us, nor will it be used or shared in a manner that differs from what is described and agreed in this Privacy Policy, without the registered user's prior consent. 

User's personally identifiable information will be sent to or shared with third-parties only when:   
  1\. User's give their consent to share the information   
Or  
  2\. Our legal business partners or external agencies those are obligated to us in terms of confidentiality agreements

Or

  4\. Respond to your comments to resolve any issue   
Or  
  5\. Respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government regulatory or security, etc   
Or   
  6\. Required by law for any legal process / summons served on **HopAroundIndia.com**

Advertisements

Every time a user visits our website and later on other websites third-party advertising companies enrolled by us will track the user browsing to know about goods and services that interest you. These companies serve ads and in the process of reaching to you may use your details (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) and in case you would like to have detailed information about this practice and may want to exercise your choice to block your details being used by any of these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Amendments 

The last time we revised our policy was on 20th November 2011. However, **HopAroundIndia.com** retains the rights to amend or change this policy without prior notice. Any such change(s) regarding the same shall be posted on this page for which we strongly recommend you to return to this page from time to time for any sort of updates.  The information displayed on this website can be re-publishing or distributed only by written consent. 

The statement and policies mentioned above are not intended directly or indirectly to create any contractual or any legal rights on behalf of any party. If you have questions about our privacy statement or our use of your information, or if you need help changing the information provided to us, please [contact us](http://www.hoparoundindia.com/footer/getintouch.aspx).
